var init = { "questions": [ {"question": "Which cursor follows the roll of the mouse and becomes an arrow when positioned outside the page borders?", "answers": ["I-beam cursor	","Flashing cursor","Insertion point cursor","	Q-beam cursor"], "correctAnswer": 1},{"question": "Which cursor indicates the location of the user in the document?", "answers": ["I-beam cursor","Flashing cursor","Mouse point cursor","Q-beam cursor "], "correctAnswer": 2},{"question": "What is the function of word wrap?", "answers": ["It transports the line that will not fit on the current page to the next page.","It transports the cursor to the other page.","It transports any words that wonâ€™t fit on the current line to the next line along with the cursor.","It moves the cursor as the user types along."], "correctAnswer": 3},{"question": "What key does the user utilize to delete a character to the left or behind the insertion point?", "answers": ["Backspace key","Delete key	","Enter key","Tab key"], "correctAnswer": 1},{"question": "Which key places a hidden character into the document that instructs the word processor to go to the next line?", "answers": ["Backspace key	","Delete key","Enter key ","Tab key"], "correctAnswer": 3},{"question": "What is the function of the arrow keys?", "answers": ["To draw an arrow","To take you over characters that are placed in the document","To locate the cursor","To locate the I-beam cursor"], "correctAnswer": 2},{"question": "What is the function of the UNDO option?", "answers": ["Allows the user to edit a word","Allows the user to undo the last thing you did","Allows the user to undo the last letter","Allows the user to undo the last line"], "correctAnswer": 2},{"question": "When instructions call for you to hit any key, what does that mean?", "answers": ["To press any key on the keyboard","To press the key labeled any key","To press the Esc key","To press the Delete key"], "correctAnswer": 1},{"question": "What is the function of the Number Lock key?", "answers": ["To delete any numbers in the document","To use the Function keys","To add any number to the document","To use the numbers in the key pad"], "correctAnswer": 4},{"question": "Word wrap is when", "answers": ["a word is too long to fit on a line and is deleted by the word processor.","the word processor hyphenates a word at the end of a line.","the word processor determines if there is room for a word at the end of a line or if it should go to the next line.","the typist determines where one line of text ends and the next begins."], "correctAnswer": 3}]};